https://www.solihull.ac.uk/about-us/policies/

INTRANET
Menu16 – 19Introduction16 – 19 CoursesOur Courses vs A-LevelsFast Forward Careers ExplorerOur CampusesHow do I apply?University CentreVirtual Open EventStudent ServicesDigital InnovatorsInformation for ParentsInformation for Schools16-17 Railcard CloseBecome anApprenticeIntroductionApprenticeshipsHow do I apply?Apprenticeship vacanciesEmploy an apprenticeOur CampusesStudent Services CloseUniversity LevelLearnerIntroductionUniversity Level CoursesChoosing the right courseStudent ServicesPolicies and Applicant InformationHow do I apply?Higher Education – Coronavirus FAQOur CampusesVirtual Open EventGraduation 2020About Birmingham and SolihullMeet the TeamProgramme SpecificationsUniversity Centre Information ClosePart TimeLearnerIntroductionPart Time CoursesProspectus PDFHow to Apply and EnrolFree Part Time CoursesReignite Your FutureChoosing the right courseFinance and LoansOur CampusesStudent Services CloseManagement &ProfessionalIntroductionManagement & Professional CoursesOur CampusesChoosing the right courseStudent Services CloseOnlineLearnerIntroductionOnline CoursesOnline Construction coursesDistance Learning CloseEmployersIntroductionShort CoursesHelping Your BusinessEmploy An ApprenticeEmployers & Apprentices Coronavirus FAQLeadership and ManagementWork Experience / Industry PlacementsBusiness Elevator ProjectBusiness Elevator ResourcesConference Centre CloseNews &EventsVirtual Open EventsTerm DatesLatest NewsEnrolment Details CloseOurCollegeAbout UsOur Campuses360 Tour – Look InsideOfsted ReportMission and ValuesEquality & DiversitySafeguarding & PreventJobsStudent ProfilesSeptember: Latest UpdatesInstitute of TechnologyStudent VoicePoliciesSenior Leadership TeamCollege GovernanceAlumniLove Our CollegesSolihull Venue HireAspire Hair & BeautyClub VitalizeSupplying to Solihull CollegeStudent ServicesFast Forward Careers ExplorerCreate Central BootcampsContact Us Close
Menu
MENU
close menue
16 – 19
Introduction
16 – 19 Courses
Our Courses vs A-Levels
Fast Forward Careers Explorer
How do I apply?
Our Campuses
University Centre
Virtual Open Event
Student Services
Digital Innovators
Information for Parents
Information for Schools
16-17 Railcard
Apprentice
Introduction
Apprentice
How do I apply?
Apprenticeship vacancies
Employ an apprentice
Our Campuses
Student Services
University Level Learner
Introduction
University Level Courses
Policies and Applicant Information
Choosing the right course
Graduation 2020
How do I apply?
Our Campuses
Virtual Open Event
Student Services
About Birmingham and Solihull
Meet the Team
University Centre Information
Programme Specifications
Part Time Learner
arrow--right
AdmissionsData ProtectionEquality & DiversityFeesFreedom of InformationGeneralHigher EducationSafeguarding & PreventStrategyStudent ServicesSupply Chain and SubcontractingTrade Union
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Admissions
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Admissions Policy (Further Education)Admissions Policy (Higher Education)Admissions Appeal Procedure (Higher Education)
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Return to Top
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Data Protection
For any Data Protection requests or enquiries, please contact the Data Protection Officer. Please contact the College via data.protection@solihull.ac.uk.
Solihull College & University Centre’s privacy policies (below) have been created in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (“GDPR”) and the Data Protection Act 2018.
Staff, students and others have the right to gain access to any personal data that is being kept about them either on computer or in certain files. The College’s Privacy Policies for staff, students and others show all the types of data the College holds about them and processes, and the reasons for which it is processed.
Any person who wishes to gain access to such personal data should make a Subject Access Request by contacting the College via the mailbox data.protection@solihull.ac.uk and refer to the Data Protection Policy (below).
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Data Protection PolicyGeneral Privacy PolicyPrivacy Policy – StaffPrivacy Policy – Students
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Return to Top
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Equality & Diversity
At Solihull College, we are committed to ensuring our environment is both diverse and free from discrimination. We are committed to ensuring that every member of staff and our students feels safe and confident in our College.
Solihull College values diversity and welcomes all those who value an excellent education regardless of their age, race, gender, religion disability or sexual orientation.
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Statement of Commitment to Students with Learning Difficulties and DisabilitiesGender Pay Gap Analysis 2019Gender Pay Gap Analysis 2018Gender Pay Gap Analysis 2017Equality Policy Equality & Diversity Annual Report 2019Equality & Diversity Annual Report 2018Equality & Diversity Annual Report 2017Equality & Diversity Annual Report 2016Equality & Diversity Annual Report 2015Equality & Diversity Annual Report 2014Equality & Diversity Annual Report 2013Equality & Diversity Annual Report 2012
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Return to Top
close
arrow--right
Tuition Fees PolicyTuition Fees Policy (Higher Education)Finance Payments for UK and EU Students
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Return to Top
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Freedom of Information
In accordance with the Freedom of Information Act 2000, you may request recorded information held by Solihull College & University Centre which is not personal, commercially sensitive or would otherwise come within the exemptions in the Act, or would be contrary to other legislation or common law principles.
Personal Data:
Requests for personal data do not fall within the Freedom of Information and are dealt with as above via the mailbox data.protection@solihull.ac.uk.
Freedom of Information requests:
A fee may be charged by Solihull College
& University Centre
in response to your freedom of information request. This will be assessed on a case by case basis. In the event that Solihull College & University Centre decides to charge a fee, it will send you a fees notice.
Solihull College & University Centre will respond to such a request for information normally within 20 working days of the receipt of your request.
Applications for Freedom of information can be made by email: public@solihull.ac.uk.
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Freedom of Information Publication Scheme
close
arrow--right
AA for Exams Guidance Policies and Processes 2020-2021Academic Appeals ProcedureAcademic Appeals Procedure (Higher Education)Anti- Bribery and Corruption PolicyAssessment Malpractice Policy (Extract)Careers Education and Guidance PolicyCode of Ethics and Conduct for Staff and GovernorsComplaints & Concern PolicyDisability Policy Exams 2020-2021E-Communications PolicyExpenses and Benefits ProceduresFitness to Study PolicyHarassment Policy (Students)Health and Safety PolicyModern Slavery Human Trafficking StatementSmoking PolicyStudent Charter PolicyStudent Disciplinary ProcedureStudent Code of ConductSustainability and Environment Development PolicyTravel PlanValue for Money PolicyWhistleblowing PolicyWord Processor Policy for Exams 2020-2021
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Return to Top
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Higher Education
Please note that for the 2020/2021 academic year our policies and procedures may be modified due to the ongoing Coronavirus (COVID-19) pandemic. Our higher education (HE) partners and Solihull College & University Centre may adapt regulations to ensure that our students are not disadvantaged.
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Access & Participation Plan 2020/21 - 2024/25Access & Participation Plan 2019/20Access Agreement 2018/19Access Agreement 2017/18Accreditation of Prior Learning Policy (Higher Education)Course Closure Policy (Higher Education)External Examiners Policy (Higher Education)Programme Validation & Revalidation Policy (Higher Education)Student Compensation Policy (Higher Education)Student Protection Plan (Higher Education)Teaching, Learning, Assessment & Scholarship Strategy (Higher Education)Transparency Return
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Return to Top
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Safeguarding & Prevent
The College is committed to providing a safe environment for young people and vulnerable adults, identifying young people and vulnerable adults who are suffering, or likely to suffer, significant harm and to taking appropriate action to ensure that such young people and vulnerable adults are kept safe, both at home and at the College.
The College is also committed to providing students with the necessary skills and knowledge to keep themselves and others safe. Education, like other key sectors, has a responsibility to promote values of openness and tolerance and to facilitate free debate which is characteristic of being a British citizen.
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Safeguarding Young People and Vulnerable Adults PolicyPolicy to Prevent Radicalisation & Violent ExtremismPolicy for Organising Events With External SpeakersFreedom of Speech PolicyAppendix - Safeguarding young people and vulnerable adults during Coronavirus COVID-19
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Return to Top
close
arrow--right
Strategic Plan and Annual PrioritiesUniversity Level Strategy
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Return to Top
close
arrow--right
Careers and Guidance PolicyFinancial Assistance Guidelines (16 to 19 year olds)Financial Assistance Guidelines (Adults)Policy Statement on Provider and Employer Access
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Return to Top
close
arrow--right
Subcontracting PolicySubcontracting Fees and Charges 2019-2020Subcontracting Fees and Charges 2018-2019Subcontracting Fees and Charges 2018-2019 AddendumSubcontracting Fees and Charges 2017-2018Subcontracting Fees and Charges 2017-2018 Addendum
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Return to Top
close
arrow--right
Trade Union Facility Time Report 2019/2020 1Trade Union Facility Time Report 2018/2019 1Trade Union Facility Time Report 2017/2018 1
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
1 In accordance with the Trade Union (Facility Time Publication Requirements) Regulations 2017, the College is required to publish certain information on trade union officials and facility time.
close
closeclose
close
close
arrow--left
arrow--right
Return to Top
close
CookiesThis site uses cookies:
Find out more here.Okay, thanks
